Guide to the Human Rights Watch records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series 2: Country Files, 1978-1997
  - Mix of Correspondence, Articles and Reports, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 11)
  - Mon
  - Mon National Relief Committee Monthly Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 381, Folder 12)
  - "The New Mon State Party", 1995 (Box 381, Folder 13)
  - Situation, 1991-1994 (Box 381, Folder 14)
  - Muslim Minority, 1985 1991 (Box 381, Folder 15)
  - NGOs
  - Burma, 1993-1994 (Box 381, Folder 16)
  - Other, 1992-1994 (Box 381, Folder 17)
  - United States, 1993-1994 (Box 381, Folder 18)
  - News Clips, 1992-1993, (6 folders) (Box 381, Folder 19-24)
  - News Clips, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 382, Folder 1-2)
  - "The Numbers of Political Prisoners Released from Prisons or Under House Arrest", 1992 (Box 382, Folder 3)
  - "Old Documents", 1988-1992 (Box 382, Folder 4)
  - Open Society Fund, Inc., 1992 (Box 382, Folder 5)
  - Open Society Institute--Burma Project, 1994 (Box 382, Folder 6)
  - Political Opposition
  - General, 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 382, Folder 7-9)
  - Abuses, 1989-1991 (Box 382, Folder 10)
  - Opposition Groups, 1990-1993 (Box 382, Folder 11)
  - Organizations in Thailand, 1993-1994 (Box 382, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations, 1991-1993 (Box 382, Folder 13)
  - Other Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 382, Folder 14)
  - Overseas National Students Organization of Burma, 1992-1993 (Box 382, Folder 15)
  - Porters
  - General, 1988-1989 (Box 382, Folder 16)
  - Press, 1989-1991 (Box 382, Folder 17)
  - Project Maje, 1991-1994 (Box 382, Folder 18)
  - Testimonies, 1992-1993 (Box 382, Folder 19)
  - Refugees
  - In Thailand, 1990-1994, (2 folders) (Box 382, Folder 20-21)
  - Rohingya
    - General, 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box 382, Folder 22-23)
    - Fax letters, 1992 (Box 382, Folder 24)
    - Relocations, 1992-1993 (Box 382, Folder 25)
    - Sanctions, 1990 (Box 382, Folder 26)
    - Sein Win, 1995 (Box 382, Folder 27)
    - Shan Human Rights Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 382, Folder 28)
    - State Law and Order Restoration Council (SLORC)
    - General, 1988-1990 (Box 382, Folder 29)
    - Economic Delegation to U.S., 1993-1994 (Box 382, Folder 30)
    - Forced Labor, 1994-1995 (Box 382, Folder 31)
    - Law and Notification, 1994-1995 (Box 382, Folder 32)
    - Speeches, 1994-1995 (Box 382, Folder 33)
    - Statements, 1992 (Box 382, Folder 34)
  - Steele, Doug--Correspondence, 1993 (Box 382, Folder 35)
  - Students, 1988-1991 1994, (2 folders) (Box 382, Folder 36-37)
  - Students on Border, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - Telexes, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 2)
  - Tourism, 1994-1995 (Box 383, Folder 3)
  - Trade and Aid, 1989-1991 (Box 383, Folder 4)
  - Tribal and Ethnic Groups, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 5)
  - United Nations
  - General, 1991 (Box 383, Folder 6)
  - Children's Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 383, Folder 7)
  - Development Programme (UNDP), 1994 (Box 383, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly
  - General, 1992-1994 (Box 383, Folder 9)
  - Burma, 1991-1992 (Box 383, Folder 10)
  - High Commissioner for Refugees, 1991-1994 (Box 383, Folder 11)
  - United States
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1989-1991 (Box 383, Folder 12)
  - Drug Enforcement Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 383, Folder 13)
  - Official Papers, 1991-1995 (Box 383, Folder 14)
  - Policy, 1989-1995, (6 folders) (Box 383, Folder 15-20)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees, 1990-1993 (Box 383, Folder 21)
  - Women
  - AIDS and Human Rights, 1989 1992-1993 (Box 383, Folder 22)
  - Asia Watch (AW) Trips, 1992-1993
    - Policy/Notes, 1992 (Box 383, Folder 23)
    - Reports directly relevant to September Trip, 1992 (Box 383, Folder 24)
    - Trip Notes & Report, 1992 September -October (Box 383, Folder 25)
    - Background Info. 0n Burma, undated (Box 383, Folder 26)
    - Child Protection--UN: "Promotion and Protection of the Rights of Children", 1994 October (Box 383, Folder 27)
    - Groups in Thailand on Women's Issues, 1992 (Box 383, Folder 28)
    - Other NGOs on Women's Issues, 1992 (Box 383, Folder 29)
    - Papers on Women's Issues, 1992 (Box 383, Folder 30)
    - Trafficking Women, 1992-1994 (Box 383, Folder 31)
    - Women's Articles, 1993-1994 (Box 383, Folder 32)
    - World Peace Foundation Reports, 1997 (Box 383, Folder 33)
    - Ye-Tavoy Railway Construction: Report on Forced Labor in the Mon State and Tenasserim Division in Burma, 1994 April (Box 383, Folder 34)
    - Yuzana, Khin, 1989-1990 1994 (Box 383, Folder 35)
    - Cambodia (Box 384)
    - Asia Watch
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 384, Folder 1)
    - Press, 1990-1993 (Box 384, Folder 2)
    - Work, 1991-1995, (2 folders) (Box 384, Folder 3-4)
    - Amnesty International (AI), 1997 (Box 384, Folder 5)
    - Arms Sales, undated (Box 384, Folder 6)
    - Arrests and Releases, 1992 (Box 384, Folder 7)
    - Articles, 1991 (Box 384, Folder 8)
    - Association of Human Rights in Cambodia, 1991 December 10 (Box 384, Folder 9)
    - Cambodia Report, 1989-1993, (3 folders) (Box 384, Folder 10-12)
    - Cambodia--United Nations--Bangkok Post, 1992 April -May (Box 384, Folder 13)
    - Campaign to Oppose the Return of the Khmer Rouge, undated (Box 384, Folder 14)
    - Charter 89 Society, 1990-1993 (Box 384, Folder 15)
    - Civil Rights/Reform, 1990-1991 (Box 384, Folder 16)
    - Coalition for Peace and Reconciliation, 1991-1996, (2 folders) (Box 384, Folder 17-18)
    - Communication--Government, 1992 (Box 384, Folder 19)
    - Contacts, 1992 undated, (2 folders) (Box 384, Folder 20-21)
    - Correspondence--General, 1990-1995, (3 folders) (Box 384, Folder 22-24)
    - Criminality, 1989-1991 (Box 384, Folder 25)
    - Displacement of Civilians--Forced Conscription--Militia, 1991 (Box 384, Folder 26)
    - European Far Eastern Research Center, 1991-1993 (Box 384, Folder 27)
    - Faxes, letters, other things pending, 1990-1992 (Box 384, Folder 28)
    - Foreign Broadcast Information Service (FBIS)--Daily Reports, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 384, Folder 29-30)
    - Foreign Broadcast Information Service (FBIS)--Daily Reports, 1989 (Box 385, Folder 1)
    - Fighting, 1990-1991 (Box 385, Folder 2)
    - Forcible Relocation, 1989 (Box 385, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Relations, 1992 (Box 385, Folder 4)
    - General, 1984 1988-1993, (15 folders) (Box 385, Folder 5-19)
    - Government--Communication, 1992-1994 (Box 386, Folder 1)
    - "Human Rights Aspects of a Comprehensive Solution to the Conflict in Cambodia" (Cambodia Documentation Commission), undated (Box 386, Folder 2)
    - "Human Rights for Health Professionals in Cambodia" (American Refugee Committee), 1993 (Box 386, Folder 3)
    - Human Rights Violations, 1988-1991 (Box 386, Folder 4)
    - Humanitarian Assistance in Cambodia, 1993 (Box 386, Folder 5)
    - Indiscriminate Shelling, 1989-1991 (Box 386, Folder 6)
    - "Internally Displaced Persons in Cambodia: Needs Assessment Report", 1991 March (Box 386, Folder 7)
    - International Human Rights Organizations, 1990-1992 (Box 386, Folder 8)
    - Khmer People's National Liberation Front (KPNLF)--Abuses, 1990-1991 (Box 386, Folder 9)
    - Khmer Rouge
    - General, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 386, Folder 10-12)
    - Abuses, 1991-1992 (Box 386, Folder 13)
  - "The Khmer Rouge: A Human Rights Report", 1988 December (Box 386, Folder 14)
  - Land Issues, 1990 (Box 386, Folder 15)
  - Land Mines
  - General, 1990-1992 (Box 386, Folder 16)
  - Illustrations, undated (Box 386, Folder 17)
  - "Land Mines in Cambodia", 1991 September 25 (Box 386, Folder 18)
  - Legal System/Texts, 1989-1992 (Box 386, Folder 19)
  - Military and Government, 1990-1992 (Box 386, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1990 (Box 386, Folder 21)
  - Missions/Visits, 1988-1992 1994, (2 folders) (Box 386, Folder 22-23)
  - Negotiations--Settlement, 1990-1991 (Box 386, Folder 24)
  - Opposition Abuses, 1992 (Box 386, Folder 25)
  - Out of Question from Any of the Topics, 1989-1990 (Box 386, Folder 26)
  - Papers
  - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 386, Folder 27)
  - Notes, 1990 (Box 386, Folder 28)
  - Peace Negotiations, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 387, Folder 1-2)
  - Peace Talks--ASEAN Negotiations, 1992 (Box 387, Folder 3)
  - Phnom Penh, 1990 (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 387, Folder 5-6)
  - Prisoners, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 387, Folder 7-8)
  - Prisons
  - Conditions, 1987-1990 (Box 387, Folder 9)
  - Prisoners, 1989-1992 (Box 387, Folder 10)
  - Rebels--General, 1990 (Box 387, Folder 11)
  - Refugee Camps, 1990-1991 (Box 387, Folder 12)
  - Refugees, 1991-1992 (Box 387, Folder 13)
  - Religion, 1991-1992 (Box 387, Folder 14)
  - Repatriation of Cambodians, 1990-1992 (Box 387, Folder 15)
  - Reports (Box 388)
  - Border Reports/Others, 1991-1993 (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Committee for Co-ordination of Services to Displaced Persons in Thailand (CCSDPT) on Cambodia, 1991-1992 (Box 388, Folder 2)
  - Kiernan, Ben--Reports, undated (Box 388, Folder 3)
  - Landau, 1991 (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Reports on Factions and the State of Cambodia (SOC), 1990-1991 (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Return to Cambodia Border Khmer, 1989-1994 (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Roger Normand's Cambodia File (1993 Mission), 1993 (Box 388, Folder 7)
  - Sarpordarmean Kampuchea Daily Bulletin, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 388, Folder 8-9)
  - Sihanouk, 19881991, (2 folders) (Box 388, Folder 10-11)
  - Tan Tang--Asylum File, 1991 (Box 388, Folder 12)
  - Testimony, 1991 April (Box 388, Folder 13)
  - Thailand--Role of, 1990-1991 (Box 388, Folder 14)
  - Trips, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 388, Folder 15-16)
  - United Nations
  - General, 1989-1991 1996 (Box 388, Folder 17)
  - High Commissioner for Refugees
  - Refugees, 1991-1992 (Box 388, Folder 18)
  - Repatriation of Cambodians, 1991-1992 (Box 388, Folder 19)
  - Permanent Mission of Cambodia, 1990-1991 (Box 388, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1991-1992 (Box 388, Folder 21)
  - Security Council, 1991-1992 (Box 388, Folder 22)
  - Transitional Authority in Cambodia (UNTAC), 1991-1994, (2 folders) (Box 389, Folder 1-2)
  - United States
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1991-1992 (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Statements, 1989-1992 (Box 389, Folder 4)
  - Policy, 1989-1991, (4 folders) (Box 389, Folder 5-8)
  - Subcommittee on East Asian and Pacific Affairs, 1993 November (Box 389, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Catholic Conference and Royal Thai Government, 1992 (Box 389, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees, 1992 (Box 389, Folder 11)
  - Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children, 1991 (Box 389, Folder 12)
  - China
  - Asia Watch
  - Work, 1989-1993, (6 folders) (Box 389, Folder 13-18)
  - Congressional Work, 1990-1991 (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - Memos, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 390, Folder 3-4)
  - Press about Asia Watch (AW), 1990-1995, (5 folders) (Box 390, Folder 5-9)
  - Press Releases, 1991-1996, (2 folders) (Box 390, Folder 10-11)
  - Published Articles, 1991-1992 (Box 390, Folder 12)
  - Reports
  - Japan Mission, 1993 (Box 390, Folder 13)
  - Prison Labor Report, 1991 (Box 390, Folder 14)
  - Workers Rights, 1994 March 11 (Box 390, Folder 15)
  - A Changing China, 1991-1992 (Box 390, Folder 16)
  - Academic Education, 1993-1994 (Box 390, Folder 17)
  - Academic Freedom
  - Articles, 1989-1992 (Box 390, Folder 18)
  - General, 1991-1992 (Box 390, Folder 19)
  - Institutional Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 390, Folder 20)
  - Scientific Exchange, 1991-1993 (Box 390, Folder 21)
  - Specific Cases, 1989-1993 (Box 390, Folder 22)
  - Study Abroad--"Brain Drain", 1992-1993 (Box 390, Folder 23)
  - Academic Reform, 1992-1993 (Box 390, Folder 24)
  - Academics, 1990-1995, (3 folders) (Box 390, Folder 25-27)
  - Administrative Detention in China, undated (Box 390, Folder 28)
    [restricted until 2081]
  - Adoption (Box 391)
  - Program, 1990 (Box 391, Folder 1)
  - Project, 1990-1991 (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - AIDS and Homosexuality, 1993-1995 (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1990 (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - American Bar Association (ABA), 1989-1991 (Box 391, Folder 5)
  - Amnesty International (AI)
  - Arrests, 1989-1992 (Box 391, Folder 6)
  - Death Penalty (DP) Executions, 1989-1992 (Box 391, Folder 7)
  - General, 1990-1994 (Box 391, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Press, 1990-1992 (Box 391, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1990 (Box 391, Folder 10)
  - Anthems of Defeat: The Crackdown in Hunan Province, 1989-1992--"Hunan Report", 1992 May (3 folders) (Box 391, Folder 11-13)
  - Arms
  - General, 1992-1993 (Box 391, Folder 14)
  - Military, 1993 (Box 391, Folder 15)
  - Arrests to 1991 March 1 (Box 391, Folder 16-17)
  - Arrests to 1991 March 1 (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Arrests since, 1989 May (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Arrests, 1989-1990, (4 folders) (Box 392, Folder 3-6)
    - Lists
    - General, 1990-1991 (Box 392, Folder 7)
    - Human Rights in China, 1993 (Box 392, Folder 8)
    - Intellectuals and Students, 1989 (Box 392, Folder 9)
    - June 4th China Support, 1989-1992 (Box 392, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 392, Folder 11)
    - PEN, 1992 (Box 392, Folder 12)
    - Workers, 1991-1992 (Box 392, Folder 13)
    - Arrests/Sentences, undated, (3 folders) (Box 392, Folder 14-16)
    - Article 19 (Box 393)
      - "China's Challenge: Freedom of Expression in Hong Kong" (1996 Annual Report)", 1996 June 30 (Box 393, Folder 1)
      - Draft of World Report--Entry on China, 1989 December (Box 393, Folder 2)
      - Articles and Papers
      - Chinese language, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 393, Folder 3-5)
      - English language, 1989-1990 (Box 393, Folder 6)
      - Asian-American Free Labor Institute, 1987 undated (Box 393, Folder 7)
      - Asian Development Bank (ADB), 1994 (Box 393, Folder 8)
      - Association for Promoting Democracy in China (AFPDC)--News Clips--Chinese, undated (Box 393, Folder 9)
      - Asylum
      - General, 1989-1996 (Box 393, Folder 10)
      - Group Cases, 1993 1995 (Box 393, Folder 11)
      - Individual Cases, 1992-1997 (Box 393, Folder 12)
      - Inner Mongolia--Tsengelt Gonchigsuren--Asylum Application, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 393, Folder 13-14)
        [restricted until 2069]
      - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1984 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 393, Folder 15-16)
    - Baber, Mark--Imprisonment, 1994 (Box 393, Folder 17)
      [restricted until 2070]
    - Background--General, 1989 (Box 393, Folder 18)
    - Beijing Workers Autonomous Federation-North American Committee (BWAF-NAC), 1990-1992 (Box 393, Folder 19)
    - Bi-lateral dialogue, 1995 (Box 393, Folder 20)
    - Bills/Proposed Legislation, 1990-1991 (Box 393, Folder 21)
    - Canadian Documentation Centre--Issue Papers, 1989 (Box 393, Folder 22)
    - Caocaiyun, 1990-1993 (Box 393, Folder 23)
    - Cao, Changqing, 1990 (Box 394, Folder 1)
    - Cartoons, 1990-1993 (Box 394, Folder 2)
    - Censorship, 1989-1991 (Box 394, Folder 3)
    - Center for Modern China--Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 394, Folder 4)
    - Chen, Mingyuan--Poems, 1988 (Box 394, Folder 5)
    - China Daily--Indices, 1990 (Box 394, Folder 6)
    - China Forum Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 394, Folder 7)
    - China Freedom & Democracy Party, 1990 (Box 394, Folder 8)
    - China Human Rights Program--Columbia University, 1990 April 13 (Box 394, Folder 9)
    - China Information: The Documentation and Research Centre for Contemporary China, 1989-1995, (4 folders) (Box 394, Folder 10-13)
    - China Scholars Coordinating Committee--China Update, 1989-1990 (Box 394, Folder 14)
    - China Spring/China Alliance, 1989-1991 (Box 394, Folder 15)
    - "China Targets Activists", 1994 July (Box 394, Folder 16)
    - "China's Ultra-Left on Trial", undated (Box 394, Folder 17)
    - Chinese Alliance for Democracy
    - Members arrested in Bangkok, 1992 July 8 (Box 394, Folder 18)
    - The Voice of Democracy in China, 1991 (Box 394, Folder 19)
  - Chinese Communist Party (CCP)
  - 14th Party Congress, 1992 October (Box 394, Folder 20)
  - Party Ideology, 1990-1995, (2 folders) (Box 394, Folder 21-22)
  - Peng, Li, 1993 (Box 394, Folder 23)
  - Personnel--Defections, 1990-1993 (Box 394, Folder 24)
  - Purges, 1991 (Box 394, Folder 25)
  - Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 394, Folder 26)
  - Chinese Fellowships--Post-Tiananmen (Soros Fund)
  - Cash Account, 1989-1991 (Box 394, Folder 27)
  - Chen Yizi;s story about Soros Event, 1989 October (Box 394, Folder 28)
  - Chinese Students
  - Applicants, 1989-1990 (Box 394, Folder 29)
    [restricted until 2066]
  - Asia Watch--Work--Funding, 1989 (Box 394, Folder 30)
  - Fellowships, 1989 (Box 394, Folder 31)
  - Conference--Notes, 1992 (Box 394, Folder 32)
  - Dissidents, 1989-1993, (2 folders) (Box 394, Folder 33-34)
  - Fund Recipients, 1989-1991 (Box 394, Folder 35)
  - Soros/China Fund, 1990 (Box 394, Folder 36)
  - Chinese Hypocrisy, 1995-1996 (Box 394, Folder 37)
  - Chinese Immigration, 1993 (Box 394, Folder 38)
  - Chinese Information Center, 1989-1990 (Box 394, Folder 39)
  - Chinese Institute for Peace & Development Studies, 1990 (Box 394, Folder 40)
  - Chinese Students (Box 395)
  - Case Documentation, 1991 (Box 395, Folder 1)
  - Other Countries--Post-Tiananmen Refugees, 1991-1992 (Box 395, Folder 2)
  - Thailand, 1991 (Box 395, Folder 3)
  - United States and Canada, 1989-1991 (Box 395, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University Students Association, 1989 (Box 395, Folder 5)
  - Committee for Concerned Scientists, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 395, Folder 6)
  - Committee to End the Chinese Gulag
  - List of Prisoners, 1991 (Box 395, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, Reports, Letters, 1989-1992 (Box 395, Folder 8)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists
  - Appeals--Lists of Imprisoned Journalists, 1989-1991 (Box 395, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1989-1991 (Box 395, Folder 10)
  - Communications w/Government, 1992-1993 (Box 395, Folder 11)
  - Conferences--General, 1993 (Box 395, Folder 12)
  - Confidential Meeting--State Department, 1992-1993 (Box 395, Folder 13)
  - Contacts
  - General, 1989-1991 1994-1996, (4 folders) (Box 395, Folder 14-16)
  - Press/Government, 1989-1991 (Box 395, Folder 17)
  - Continued Repression, 1990-1991 (Box 395, Folder 18)
  - Copyright Law/Intellectual Property, 1991-1992 (Box 395, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1995, (8 folders) (Box 395, Folder 20-27)
  - Corruption
  - Cases, 1992-1995, (2 folders) (Box 395, Folder 28-29)
  - Police Brutality, 1993-1994 (Box 395, Folder 30)
  - Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 395, Folder 31)
  - Cost of Putting Business First"(HRW/Asia Report), 1996 (Box 396, Folder 1)
  - Crime--General, 1992-1995 (Box 396, Folder 2)
  - Criminal Law
  - General, 1980-1982 (Box 396, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Law Encyclopedia--Table of Contents, 1992 (Box 396, Folder 4)
  - Criminal Procedure, 1996 (Box 396, Folder 5)
  - Cui Jian 1991 (Box 396, Folder 6)
  - Dai Qing undated (Box 396, Folder 7)
  - Death Penalty
  - General, 1989 (Box 396, Folder 8)
  - Two Years After Tiananmen, 1991 May 30 (Box 396, Folder 9)
  - Defections, 1989-1990 (Box 396, Folder 10)
  - Democracy for China Fund, Inc., 1990-1992 (Box 396, Folder 11)
  - Democracy Groups, 1990 (Box 396, Folder 12)
  - "Democracy Wall Prisoners" (HRW/Asia Report), 1993 March28 (Box 396, Folder 13)
  - Demonstrations, 1989-1992, (6 folders) (Box 396, Folder 14-19)
  - Deng Xiaoping (1904-1997)
  - Death, 1997 February (Box 396, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Demonstrations, 1989 May -June (Box 396, Folder 21)
  - Disappearances--List, 1992 June (Box 396, Folder 22)
  - Discontented People in China, 1990 (Box 396, Folder 23)
  - Dissidents, 1990-1995, (5 folders) (Box 396, Folder 24-28)
  - Drugs
  - Crime, 1990-1993 (Box 396, Folder 29)
  - Executions, 1992-1995 (Box 396, Folder 30)
  - EC (European Commission) Delegation--Human Rights, 1991-1992 (Box 396, Folder 31)
  - Economy (Box 397)
  - Background, 1993-1994 (Box 397, Folder 1)
  - Decentralization, 1994 (Box 397, Folder 2)
  - Development, 1994 (Box 397, Folder 3)
  - Domestic Issues, 1991-1993, (2 folders) (Box 397, Folder 4-5)
  - Inflation, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 397, Folder 6-7)
  - Peasant Conditions, 1993-1995 (Box 397, Folder 8)
  - Poverty, 1994 (Box 397, Folder 9)
  - Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 397, Folder 10)
  - Rural Conditions, 1994 (Box 397, Folder 11)
  - State Enterprises, 1994-1995 (Box 397, Folder 12)
  - Statistics, 1994 (Box 397, Folder 13)
  - Environment--General, 1993-1996 (Box 397, Folder 14)
  - Executions, 1989-1997, (2 folders) (Box 397, Folder 15-16)
  - Family Planning
  - Abortion, 1990-1994 (Box 397, Folder 17)
  - Academic Articles, 1986-1991 (Box 397, Folder 18)
  - Asylum
  - Case--Jan, Zhe Shung, 1993 1993 (Box 397, Folder 19)
  - Population Policy, 1989-1994 (Box 397, Folder 20)
  - Birth Control
  - Abuses, 1987-1993 (Box 397, Folder 21)
  - Floating Population, 1994 (Box 397, Folder 22)
  - General, 1986-1994 (Box 397, Folder 23)
  - Infanticide and Abandonment, 1991-1993 (Box 397, Folder 24)
  - Male Preference, 1991-1995 (Box 397, Folder 25)
  - One-Child Policy
  - Legal Issues, 1990-1994 (Box 397, Folder 26)
  - Violations, 1989 1992-1994 (Box 397, Folder 27)
  - Population Policy--Academic Articles, 1989-1990 1992 (Box 397, Folder 28)
  - Population Statistics, 1990-1993 (Box 397, Folder 29)
  - Tibet--Minorities, 1989-1990 1994 (Box 397, Folder 30)
  - Fang Lizhi--human rights activist (Box 398)
  - Campaign, 1989-1991 1993 (Box 398, Folder 1)
  - Other Correspondence, 1989-1991 1994 (Box 398, Folder 2)
  - Press,1988-1992, (3 folders) (Box 398, Folder 3-5)
  - Federation for Democratic China, 1989-1990 (Box 398, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Chinese Students and Scholars in Canada (FCSSC), 1991 (Box 398, Folder 7)
  - Foetuses, 1995 (Box 398, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Business, 1993 (Box 398, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Investment, 1991 (Box 398, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Relations/Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 398, Folder 11)
  - Former Student Leaders, 1994 (Box 398, Folder 12)
  - Forum for a Better China, 1990-1991 (Box 398, Folder 13)
  - Freedom of Assembly, 1992 1994-1995 (Box 398, Folder 14)
  - Freedom of Association, 1992 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 398, Folder 15-16)
  - Freedom of Expression, 1991-1995, (6 folders) (Box 398, Folder 17-22)
  - Freedom of the Press, 1992 (Box 398, Folder 23)
  - Freedom to Travel, 1991-1993 (Box 398, Folder 24)
  - "Future China", 1990 (Box 398, Folder 25)
  - General, 1989-1994 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box 398, Folder 26-28)
  - General, 1991-1993, (10 folders) (Box 399, Folder 1-10)
  - General--Advocacy, 1991-1994 (Box 399, Folder 11)
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT), 1993-1994 (Box 399, Folder 12)
  - Gordon, Tse, 1993 (Box 399, Folder 13)
  - Groups
  - Changsha Workers, 1993 (Box 399, Folder 14)
  - Free Trade Union of China (FTUC), 1992 (Box 399, Folder 15)
  - Poets, 1990-1992 (Box 399, Folder 16)
  - Harassment of Chinese Nationals in the United States
  - Report--U.S. Rep. Benjamin A. Gilman, 1989 (Box 399, Folder 17)
  - Secret Documents, 1990 (Box 399, Folder 18)
  - A Summary of the Meeting of Educational Counselors (Consuls) in Chinese Embassies and Consulates--Chinese, 1990 March (Box 399, Folder 19)
  - Testimony of Chinese Students in America, 1990 January (Box 399, Folder 20)
  - Health, 1991-1992 (Box 399, Folder 21)
  - Heshang,1988 (Box 399, Folder 22)
  - Hong Kong
  - Britain
  - Press Clippings--China Relations, 1991-1993 (Box 399, Folder 23)
  - Press Clippings--General, 1992-1993 1995, (3 folders) (Box 399, Folder 24-26)
  - China
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 399, Folder 27)
  - Macau Protests, 1989 May -June (Box 399, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 399, Folder 29)
  - Press Clippings, 1991-1997, (5 folders) (Box 399, Folder 30-34)
  - Hong Kong University--Press Clippings, 1989 June-July, (2 folders) (Box 400, Folder 1-2)
  - Human Rights
  - Asia Watch (AW)--Joint Projects, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 400, Folder 3-4)